Hey welcome to my studio everybody.
My name is Lars Erik Robinson.
My company is LarsEr Arts All Around Art-tainment.
You might wonder when you see caricatures in a theme park or at the pier somewhere, how do they figure out how to put the body's on these caricatures, and how they figure how to do the different poses for them.
Well obviously what I drew for these two people here, they didn't have these poses like this.
So I try to think about how there personalities are, and they tell me about what they like, and sometimes you just ask the client what are the kinds of things that you're interested in.
And usually they would tell you, "Oh I love Wonder Woman," or "I love Superman."
Okay you can go from there and illustrate that.
So how am I going to create Wonder Woman in her pose.
And how am I going to have that relate to how her picture is.
So her face was angled a little bit this way.
So when I went to go draw her body with that, I actually did.
I have her actually turn in the same direction as the face is, and having to try to create a movement with her.
And the reason I put the arm here, with the body, is you want to be able to have an inter-relation between the bigger head and the smaller body by having maybe something come out perspective.
Coming right at you.
And then one going back.
So you can tell here this arm is bigger than this one here.
So it gives it a little bit more understanding that you're actually right there with them.
On him you know I wanted to create a powerful look, and having just the buttons pop out just like Superman use to do it.
And you try to create a dimension by having his legs go back.
So if that explains to you guys a little bit more how you relate bodies with the bigger heads.
Basically sometimes you don't even have to show their neck that much, you could just show the shoulders here.
Especially on guys with big shoulder muscles.
And then I hope that explains a little bit to you more about what we go through as an artist to get our bodies on your caricatures.
Thank you guys so much.